Jennifer Mahemba

Reynoldsburg, OH 43068 jennifermahemba7_nw8@indeedemail.com 614-000000

Adaptable, lateral thinker and quick learner with extensive knowledge of accounts payable, accounts receivable and general accounting process. 8+ years of experience interpreting, analyzing and maintaining data in order to drive successful business solutions.

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

Work Experience

Accounts Payable Specialist

Ohio Transmission Corp - Columbus, OH January 2016 to Present

- Prepare invoice batches and enter information from each invoice into the system
- Improve A/P approval process reducing late fees from 40% to 10%
- Negotiate payment terms with vendor to improve cash flow and facilitate company's return to profitability
- Managed the accurate and timely processing of over 5000 invoices per month
- Supported department in all facets of month-end closing for Air Technologies vendors
- Implement technology and process automations, including EDI system
- Provide support in performing auditing procedures and ensure that any discrepancies are promptly resolved
- Reconciled vendor statements, researched and corrected discrepancies
- · Invoice total matching, two-way and three-way matching

Payment and Balancing Specialist

Payment and Balancing Specialist

ADVOCATE Radiology Billing - Columbus, OH September 2015 to January 2016

Contract)

- Monthly processing of patient statements. Answer and resolve patient billing inquires.
- Maintained insurance mapping
- Accurately apply payments to patient accounts
- Prepared reports capture verification for applicable sites
- Verified receipts and accepted ECS claims
- · Monitor ledger billing records while process data flow for electronic demographics feeds
- Received and process electronic remittance advice reports

Professional Bank Teller

PNC Financial Services Group - Columbus, OH January 2011 to January 2015

- Assisted branch manager with daily audits and vault balancing which exceeded \$50K
- Processed loans and mortgage payments for customers
- Perform account maintenance activities, including changes of address, account ownership, account type and others
- Responds to customer account inquiries totaling 120+ weekly accounts
- Develops and deepens customer relationships by providing outstanding customer service following a focused cross-selling strategy

Account Receivable Clerk / Collections

First American Loans - Columbus, OH February 2008 to December 2010

- Track all money received and prepare deposits
- Enter customer payments into the system on daily basis
- Research and resolve complex accounting issues
- Secured and negotiated payment arrangements on delinquent accounts
- · Educate customers on account terms and how to use alternate payment programs
- Performed general clerical duties including filing, bank deposits, and answering phones
- Initiate collections proceedings against past due accounts

Customer Service Specialist

Countrywide Home Loans - Dallas, TX January 2003 to January 2008

- Inbound calls responsible for loan modifications and refinance
- Correspond to inquiries regarding real estate loans in a high volume call center, regarding tax disbursements, escrow accounts, missing payment, insurance, etc.
- Keep updated and be Knowledgeable of types of loans customers have such as Conventional, FHA, and all new procedures that would come out daily to better serve our customers and third party callers
- Provide support to processors and loan officers in structuring loan deals and if necessary, rework the loan to new terms or identify additional conditions
- Verified financial ratios and credit reports ensuring completeness of application information
- Analyzed appraisals, credit reports and associated documentation, ensuring proper qualification according to Company guidelines

Education

Bachelor's Degree in Accounting

Western Governors University Present

Associate Degree in Business Management

Columbus State Community College - Columbus, OH 2014

Skills

• Excellent problem solving, organizational and decision making skills

- Vendor negotiations and management
- Ability to multitask and prioritize daily requirements
- Ability to work in a fast-paced environment with high-volume work
- Proficient knowledge in ZirMed, SX GUI, DataServ. AS 400, Lexus nexus and Genesis Teller Systems
- Good knowledge of Microsoft Excel, Word, and Outlook
- Excellent analytical, reconciliation and troubleshooting skills
- Attention to details and ability to maintain level of accuracy when entering invoices and generating reports for Cost of Goods expenditures
- Invoice
- Accounts Payable
- AP
- Concur
- Accounts Receivable